This is...
So many human organs.
What exactly is Yungong Pavilion doing?
How dare you trespass into
the forbidden area of Yungong Pavilion!
You're courting death!
Girl.
Mister.
Am I dreaming?
Girl,
wake up. You can't sleep.
The secret chamber must not be exposed.
So no matter who it is,
they must be silenced.
Master Yan,
you asked for this.
You
are not a mortal.
Hand over the antidote
if you don't want to die.
Only
the Pavilion Master
can concoct the antidote.
He is out on a tour
and hasn't returned yet.
What's wrong with you guys?
Didn't I give her
the poison-repelling bead?
How could she still be poisoned?
Senior Medical Maniac,
it's all my fault.
Please check on her first.
If there is no antidote for this poison,
she will definitely die in three days.
But I think you can also see
that there is a mysterious power
in her body
neutralizing the toxin.
So,
she will be fine.
If I'm not mistaken,
that's very likely
the power of Nuwa.
It is precisely because of this power
that I once thought of
leaving her to fend for herself.
But when she was truly hurt,
I...
Just because she possesses
the power of Nuwa,
I hurt her like this.
But when has she ever harmed me?
Girl,
who exactly are you?
What should I do with you?
This is
the Qi Residence.
My Lady, you're awake.
My master has been waiting for you.
I can finally meet my savior.
Hello,
are you the master of the Qi Residence?
I heard that you saved...
What? Haven't seen me for a few days
and you don't recognize me?
It's actually
you.
That's right.
I'm now called Qi Yan.
Master Yan,
I will keep your
life-saving grace in mind.
What did you call me?
I won't stay and bother you anymore,
nor will I reveal your identity.
Stop right there. I just saved you,
and you're leaving just like that?
Then kill me.
I'll just return this life to you.
I thought I had set up a protective seal,
thought everything was under control.
But your injury is real.
You thought my giving up on you
was also real.
About Black Wind Fort, I was wrong.
You can hate me,
or you can leave.
But I beg you to stay for three days,
until the poison is completely cleared.
In three days, wherever you want to go,
I will escort you.
Mister, you being so reasonable
all of a sudden
scares me a little.
I am not used to it either.
Then hold it in.
Do not go back on your word.
Stay. Not to be my anyone,
but to be yourself.
Are you sure?
If I am myself,
the first thing I will do is scold you.
Scold me.
Bastard!
I will take it.
Old monster!
Not that one.
Girl,
I can wait for you to trust me again.
I am hungry.
What do you want to eat?
A lot.
Qi Manor can afford it.
My savior treating me to a meal
does not mean I have no backbone.
Bastard.
I cannot believe his bathhouse has
so many things women like to use.
Then again.
Young Master Yan of Qiong City,
Master of the Yan Sect,
how could he lack women?
He actually apologized to me just now.
Could it be...
So annoying, what on earth am I thinking?
No, I cannot stay and let him bully me.
Since I am leaving,
men's clothes are definitely
more convenient.
Little one,
we meet again.
So you are Young Master Yan's
male favorite in Qi Manor.